foreign
[Music]
good to have you well you know what
thanks a lot morning Nigel morning
Prashant we all love the monsoons but
the monsoon
challenge traffic jams and all of that
and it's hard too so today I felt like I
was in an Indiana Jones movie you know
trying to make it on time and using this
road and that but in any case I mean
looks like it's going to be a good day
for the markets as well uh you know all
eyes will be on the first take this
morning which the all indications are
that the gift Nifty is showing a 30
point up move but our research team is
joining in to talk about many stocks of
course indecent bank is top of mind
because of very good set of numbers
Abhishek is here with us to give us the
fine print Abhishek morning morning
Sonia so it's an absolute Serene results
coming in from indusind Bank the balance
sheet risk is at the lowest in last uh
seven years or even more so what has
been good in the results uh or over the
last few quarters is that it is perhaps
the only Bank to see a yoy and courtroom
quarter growth in operating profits for
10 quarters in a row so net interest
margin is at eight year high on a
quarterly basis coming in at 4.29
percent the rwa Oris weight asset to
advances ratio at 111 percent is perhaps
the lowest in last seven years or even
more it used to be around 120 530
percent or you know few years back so uh
analyze slippage ratio of just 1.9
percent is perhaps the lowest in last 11
quarters and second lowest and last 16
quarters so asset quality continues to
improve gross and pay ratio of 1.94
percent and net NP ratio of 0.58 percent
are perhaps are one of the best that you
are seeing in last 10 quarters what has
not been good in the result which we
already know from the business update is
that Casa ratio has dipped below 40
percent so it's the lowest uh that you
are seeing in last six years or 24
quarters and cost to income ratio has
inched up a bit to about 45.9 percent
when compared to 44.9 percent in the
previous quarter in terms of p l
performance and as a head of our poll
while part is largely in line with apple
back to you
okay all right uh thanks a lot for that
Abhishek but Abhishek here also uh
tracking another banking name that's a
federal bank tell us more about their
fundraising plans out there
they have had a IFC or which will invest
about 959 crore into the bank via
preferential allotments so this is a
preferential Capital coming in uh to the
bank so IFC will take its holding in the
bank to about 8.1 percent uh post the
fundraise from 4.95 percent that they
had earlier what this fund infusion does
in terms of mathematics is that tier one
ratio will increase to 14.36 percent it
was at 12.54 earlier Equity dilution is
about 3.4 percent net worth will
increase by four and a half percent Book
value will increase by one person to
around rupees 107 per share a federal
bank may look to raise more money uh in
the coming period or in the near future
as well back to you
thank you very much for that now to the
I think one disappointment that we had
results came right after markets closed
yesterday Rima is here to talk about lnt
Technologies
hi morning so there is a big Revenue
Miss uh the company has reported a
dollar Revenue growth of 9.8 this is
much lower than consensus expectations
of 12 12 and a half percent growth so
big Miss on the top line uh the problem
is the organic Revenue growth remember
the company's Top Line has been boosted
by an acquisition swc acquisition but if
you strip that out organic Revenue
growth has come in below consensus at
just point six percent on a quarter on
quarter basis margins have fallen by 100
basis points to 17.2 percent on account
of the integration costs but at 17.2
percent margins it's likely better than
what the street was anticipating the
company has held on to its full year
guidance so they're still maintaining
that they will do a 20 top line growth
to analysts believe it could be a bit
challenging given the ask rate and the
soft q1 management says it was the delay
in decision making in q1 which impacted
uh the revenue performance but there has
been an improvement in decision making
in June and July which is why they're
hopeful and confident that Q2 will show
an acceleration in growth back to you
okay thanks a lot for that so big
Revenue Miss coming in there lower than
expectations the street would react to
that but let's find out how ICICI
Lombard did in their results surbi has
more details on that so be over to you
thanks so much for that so when it comes
to premium growth it was pretty much in
line with estimates but the path was
below estimates and that is largely on
account of higher losses due to Cyclone
so the premium saw growth of 19 on a
year-on-year basis Pat was up 12 on a
year-on basis the combined ratio came in
at 103.8 percent but if you exclude the
Cyclone impact it stood at 102.9 percent
versus 104.1 percent same time last year
the claims ratio also were a little
elevated due to the Cyclone but
management continues to maintain the
combine combined ratio guidance of 102
percent by fy25 but they also indicated
the claims ratio will be a little uh
elevated due to floods in North India
and that impact will be seen in Q2 so
we'll watch out for that as well okay
all right thanks for that survey and
we'll also be chatting with the
management of icsa Lombard General
Insurance later on in the show at 9 50
am
but let's hop across the sonar she's
joining in to tell us about a couple of
other numbers that came out his mother's
specialty as well as cie Automotive Sona
thank you so much for that uh well both
of them reported strong set of numbers
let me start with himadri Specialty
Chemicals it was a good set revenues
declined by nine percent on yui basis
but if you look at the ebitda and
margins there were there was an
expansion of around 600 basis points
profits were up 123 the gross debt has
also declined on a quarter one quarter
basis to come at 6.82 crore rupees the
company has acquired 12.8 in secono
limited which specializes in Silicon
anode technology which is used for
lithium-ion battery so this is once uh
expansion that they are planning as well
if we talk about the other name which is
cie Automotive uh their revenues were up
4.7 ebitda was up 21 margins were higher
by 300 basis points leading to a profit
growth of 60 those numbers were good as
well
okay well uh thanks very much sonal for
that uh now let's talk about uh earnings
from the media space Network 18 and TV
18 broadcast both reported numbers for
the first quarter surveys here with
details it'll be money morning so it was
a mixed set of numbers from them it was
they showed a strong Revenue growth but
the operating costs were higher which
led to losses operating losses but
operating costs were higher driven by
investment on expanding content coverage
and also the distribution reach so
operating revenues were of 142 percent
TV 18 operating revenues were up 26 the
entertainment segment was up 184 and the
digital was down 16 on a year-on-year
basis operating losses on a Consolidated
basis came in an 84 crores versus a
versus 75 crores the tv80 news losses
were six crores versus a loss of four
crores and the entertainment loss was 49
crores versus a profit of 62 crores same
time last year the net profit was down
26 on a Consolidated basis
okay thanks for that well Amara Raja
batteries has been in focus for the last
few days on the back of the block deal
Vivek has more details on that he's also
tracking rallies India this morning
Vivek good morning
well you know both the stocks are on our
radar and the back of you know large
blocks that happened uh in yesterday's
trading session you know like we
mentioned yesterday Amara Raja clarius
airbn holding that held a 14 stake at
the end of the June quarter yesterday
completely exited at stake you know so
now it's a clean out trade uh you know
some of the key buyers included Society
General picking up almost two and a half
percent in the block deal of BNP pariba
you know Arbitrage fund picked up almost
a percent and a half Tata AI life
insurance picked up over one person and
some of the other key buyers include
domestic mutual funds like kotak
Mahindra as well as Nippon India mutual
fund now coming to rallies uh very
interesting blog deal over there you
know sold almost 4.99 stake the entire
stake was laptop by Tata chemicals uh so
you know post this particular stake by
by Tata chemical in Dallas India their
stake has now increased to over 55
percent
um you know also sold half a percent
stake whether buyer was in a ratnapoli
investment so almost 5.04 percent stake
sold by Reika in yesterday's trading
session in Raleigh yeah okay we'll watch
out for all of these names thanks a lot
here's a quick recap of our top stocks
in case you missed out on any of course
Talk of the day could be in this in bang
post very good numbers then you have
Federal Bank icsl Lombard himadri
specialty CI Automotive Network 18 tv18
broadcast Samara Raja batteries in
rallies India while the only stock on
our radar with negative news for today
is lnt Tech but let's also get a quick
handle on what's happening in the world
of Commodities Manisha Gupta is joining
in for a Roundup of all the action there
Manisha what's been happening
thank you for that Sonia well uh we are
looking at some support coming in for
the industrial Commodities I'll start
with crude where the prices did get two
percent overnight the markets are
anticipating the U.S inventories to show
a decline that is because the output has
seen a decline and also because this is
a summer driving demand season you could
be looking at some support because of
that as well also China officials
suggesting policy rollout to support
local consumption is a positive to watch
out for the other sector which has done
quite well for itself has been the
precious metals the gold price is
searched to a seven week highs in the
overnight Market this is after a ECB has
signaled a pause on rate hike from the
month of September and we've seen the
Canadian inflation numbers also come
within their range the street will watch
out for further data coming in from
Europe in this week itself in meanwhile
it also is about uh the client that
we've seen in terms of production when
it comes to gold and silver that seems
to be supporting as well
thanks very much uh for that that's
Commodities in Focus we'll take a very
quick commercial break here David choksi
will be with us with uh what he makes if
some of these earnings which have come
through to begin with and uh what he
likes in the market we're back with that
we'll also have the CEO of healthcare
Global Enterprises to discuss their
expansion plans and the Outlook as they
see it stay with us
[Music]
foreign